Amanda Steele Show. Today's goes to Drake for pushing J. Cole right in front of Kendrick so he
can see what happens. It's definitely giving Bravo. Watch what happens now. Drake looked at
J. Cole and was like, you gonna let him say that about us? Then proceeded to watch Cole write
seven minute drill. Honestly, the most thoughtful, cordial, well-mannered diss track of all time.
Okay, his locks are messier than the raps. This may not be Jay versus Nas. It's definitely not
Beanie Siegel versus Jadakiss. And you know, some people are like, why does it take rappers going
against each other for it to be exciting? And it's like, because it just does. I don't know what
else to tell y'all. It's part of the dynamics of the genre. It just does. Today's letdown goes to
the age limit settings on Aoki Simmons Raya dating app. Aoki Simmons, daughter of Russell and Kimora
Lee Simmons, was recently seen on the beach engaged in heavy petting with a 65 year old
restauranteur, Vittorio Ossoff. Okay, let me just say this. I ain't got nothing to say about Aoki
because Aoki is 21. And at 21, you still need guidance from the people around you. So I just
named three grown people in this situation that are not doing a job. The thing about being 21 is like,
yes, you can do what you want. But the beauty of it is that when you have mentors around you,
or you have adults around you that care about you, they are able to speak into you in a way
that has you do what you want and make choices that are, you know, good for you.